# Akshay More



akshaymorejl04@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/akshaymore2018



https://akshaymore2018.github.io/

#### Summary

A fan of preparation and established fundamentals, because they give a better understanding of which rules to break, and which rules to think twice about. Expert in strategic and tactical planning. Knowledgeable about programming paradigms, design patterns, rendering pipeline stages, and optimization techniques. Experienced in game development life cycle. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Computer Science from MIT Academy of Engineering, Pune.

#### **Experience**



#### S Programmer

Sumo Digital Ltd Mar 2022 - Present (2 months +) - Gameplay & Tools

## S Junior Programmer

Sumo Digital Ltd Sep 2021 - Mar 2022 (7 months) - Gameplay

## S Junior Programmer

Sumo India Studios Aug 2020 - Jul 2021 (1 year) - C++

## Trainee Programmer

Sumo India Studios Aug 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year) - C++

#### Junior Programmer

Rendered Ideas Dec 2018 - Mar 2019 (4 months) - Java

#### Trainee Programmer

Rendered Ideas Dec 2017 - Nov 2018 (1 year) - Java

### **Education**

### MIT Academy of Engineering, Alandi, Pune

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science 2013 - 2017 Savitribai Phule Pune University

## Rendriya Vidyalaya

High School Diploma, Mathematics and Computer Science

#### **Skills**

C++ • Java • Python • Game Development • Design Patterns • Algorithms • OpenGL • Visual Studio 2017 • Tortoise SVN • Simple and Fast Multimedia Library (SFML)